Hi it's Celine and welcome to another goth fetish party outfit video and surprise
I'm already wearing the first outfit so to say actually I just wanted to wear
the top and the leggings for an intro outfit but then I kept adding stuff like
the corset, the belt, the choker and the bracelet and the shoes and now it's
already a complete look so first outfit of the video so to say anyway after the
huge success of the first video with this title I decided I have to do a
second one so I prepared some looks I think five six with this one basically
and I hope you are going to enjoy my selection of today's outfits the first
outfit is going to be all four letter and comes with a special surprise so
let's go
Okay, so first outfit, a full leather leggings and warmers from Benno von Stein, the bra
by Lumi Sonata and shoes from band and I love the leggings but I promised you a
surprise which I'm going to show you now I'm going to press this button now and I
hope you can see it but it is lit and yellow but I can change the light now
it's kind of blue green and purple white but also party so this is the fun gimmick
in this outfit a bra that has lights built in and yeah you can wear to make
party I think it's super fun it's something new it's something cool and
you can spice up the outfit by that when you turn off the lights it's just a nice
bra but this one is the party bra now oh the slow light change yeah I would
probably not wear this to my normal goth party because it's too colorful although
I could go to the cyber goth floor so industrial music which is not my kind of
music to be honest so yeah why not for cyber goth style I think this is my
favorite color because it matches my hair but now lights on and next out
Style number two, and I'm not sure what to call it.
It's PVC meets lacy mesh meets belts and harnesses whatever.
I think it's a cool look and also with the handbag here.
So just add lots and lots of stuff and to be honest I'm not sure if the choker fits
so good so I'm going to replace it with this one.
steel so it should work well with the buckles of the belt and the harness. It's
such a cute outfit with the handbag and like the miniskirt and the matching heels.
I wasn't sure about the heels and the skirt together but I think it looks good.
I like it. This is kind of my style with the harness stuff. I used to wear this
whatever you may call it, tights, fabric, lacy mesh stuff when I was younger, so in my teens.
So this is kind of walked down the memory lane but I like this new interpretation of this old stuff so to say.
This is the back view by the way. With a short mini skirt and I think this is the most gothy outfit or classic goth outfit I'm going to show you today.
The other ones are all a bit more on the fetish side or a bit more modern.
But I like how this turned out.
And now from the most goth outfit to the most fetish outfit.
A latex military style bodysuit.
And I'm going to change into that off camera.
Tada!
A latex bodysuit.
I paired it with normal black tights. Actually this is a look I would wear out also for clothing.
Like a latex bodysuit and tights. Why not? Not in summer when it's too warm though.
But I think I have one accessory I want to try with it. A hat.
It's really big. Funny joke. But I like the style. I think it completes the outfit somehow.
Like now it's a full military look. You can definitely wear to your goth party because you have all kinds of uniforms.
And uniform styles in gothic fashion. So why not in latex?
It's really dark, the outfit, like all black with a bit of silver.
The bodysuit is made by Shiitake, following Mushroom, and you can also detach the cuffs
here or whatever you may call them, I don't know.
But I think they are part of the design, so they're definitely together with the bodysuit.
you think of this latex outfit latex yay nay for goth parties did you wear latex
for clubbing tell me in the comments and I'm going to change into the next
outfit party time so this is a outfit completely by club X a dolls kill
sub-brand except for the tights I found them and the shoes which are demonia and
little warmers which I own since I was 16 so they are almost 15 years old I still have them
yay fun because they are such a good fit for this outfit and I love the overall
look it's like for a golf summer party I can imagine when it gets really hot at
at Amphifestival this would be a great outfit or at my local disco in summer
you're sweating all the time so less is more and then you'll be happy for such an outfit
oh there's some holes in the tights oops
basically I don't know I probably no tights without holes I don't know how I
I managed it but I always destroy it. Sorry! Anyway the outfit is cool. I totally dig it.
I think that's a cool look for a cool party. And I've worn this before in white for a photoshoot
and I think there are also blue ones and everyone has them so now I finally own one too. I recently
bought new lights so I have to use it because I always forget it and I can also change the
color so it's my personal disco light.
Something like that.
Now for the last outfit I have to change again and it's going to be a corset.
I
the VC outfit and yeah I have to look at myself in the mirror sorry because I can
already see the backside the skirt has lacing to you and I think it makes such
a great figure and looks awesome together with the corset and especially
the red but the color change so corset and a skirt are both from your
shape corsets. I bought the corset when I filmed a Nox on tour there and I bought
the skirt recently in Berlin and German Fittishball so I'm happy that I can
combine them. Also some pleaser heels and gloves from Kat & Samo. I opted for a
choker but I think something that would cover this area a bit better might work
as well so I have a second option a Shrug I bought a few weeks ago at the
Viggety festival in Leipzig and I have to interchange this so here we are this
is from cyber risk and the outfit just went so much over the top with the Shrug
I don't know it's even more dominant it's even more high fashion also from the back I think it
looks so cool I know it's nice which was my favorite today it's hard it's really hard I
I love this one. I think overall this one is my favorite but for clubbing I would
prefer the Dolls Kill Clubbix outfit so they share place one so to say. Yeah
these are my two favorites. I'm not sure though. I really enjoyed all the comments under the
last fetish goth party outfit video where you told me your favorites so i really hope you enjoyed
this video and you leave a thumbs up here or consider subscribing to my patreon to support
this youtube channel alrighty i still think this looks kind of piece of art the shoulder piece
and the outfit as a whole don't forget to watch the part one if you haven't watched it
Bye!